

CONTACT

- +(40) 755 934 953
- ancamatei2012@gmail.com
- 💡 Cluj-Napoca, Cluj, Romania
- in linkedin.com/in/anca-m-matei/

SKILLS

- O HTML5
- CSS (with SASS)
- JavaScript
- Angular framework
- Responsive Web Design
- Git (Github)
- Web Development
- Rapid Learning

LANGUAGES

- Romanian (Native)
- English (Fluent)
- French (Intermediate)

EDUCATION

2009-2015

UNIVERSITY OF MEDICINE AND PHARMACY 'IULIU HATIEGANU' CLUJ-NAPOCA

Bachelor of Medicine

• 2005-2009

COLEGIUL NATIONAL 'B.P.HASDEU' BUZAU High School Diploma

ANCA-MARIA MATEI

Junior Frontend Web Developer

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a JavaScript developer specializing in the Angular frontend framework, with a focus on responsive design.

With a background in medicine, I bring discipline, continuous skill development and adaptability to diverse team environments.

I am enthusiastic about joining a team where I can collaborate and benefit from mentorship opportunities to further learn and grow.

WORK EXPERIENCE

RESIDENT DOCTOR IN DIABETES 2020 - NOW

County Emergency Clinical Hospital - Cluj-Napoca

ENDOCRINOLOGIST | 2020 - 2022

Omnimedical Clinic - Cluj-Napoca

RESIDENT DOCTOR IN ENDOCRINOLOGY | 2016 - 2019

County Emergency Clinical Hospital - Cluj-Napoca

PROJECTS

Portfolio Site

ancamatei.netlify.app/

GitHub Projects

github.com/Anca2022/

- EuroTour Car Rental Angular euro-tour.netlify.app/
- Euro Tour Car Rental

resilient-choux-32abd2.netlify.app/

Kindergarden Website

elegant-hotteok-b52902.netlify.app/

Food Mine Youtube

regal-rugelach-42bd5e.netlify.app/